fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
I'm going...
to become the Hokage.
I can't lose here!
You? Hokage?!
When you're weaker than me?
I'll become... Hokage for you!
Transform!
Hey hey, are you serious?
You've been here three years
and you can't even do
a respectable transformation?!
All of you watch now!
I will absolutely someday become
the true and real Hokage!
Lame! What Hokage?!
You know deep down inside that
you can't become the Hokage.
So quit acting tough!
You're wrong Kiba-kun...
If you compete with me for
the name of Hokage...
You... will be the loser!
Hinata
Blushes!
The Crowd
Opens Their
Mouths Wide,
Naruto's
Trump
Card
Man! Same thing over and over again.
You're pesky!
Well, never mind.
I'll just make it so
you won't stand up again!
Let's go, Akamaru!
You think you can get me with
that same technique again?!
Take this!
Damn!
Fang Over Fang!
This Jutsu...
Though, I've seen it before...
it's not a Jutsu you can dodge
over and over!
What do I do?
What should I do?!
Looks like you've got nothing left.
I've got plenty left!
Even if you increased yourself by
three or four, I'd still have a lot left!
You've got a comeback
for everything!
Let's finish him with the next!
Akamaru!
Damn!
I have to counterattack somehow.
Even if I do, it has to get Kiba
or there's no point!
But which is which...?
W-What will you do? Naruto!
Naruto-kun...
T-That's it!
Transform!
You're mine!
I see how it is...
Huh?
There, look closely.
Oh!
You did it!
That's a clever move, Naruto!
Naruto-kun!
If he transforms into Kiba,
the real Kiba doesn't know which is
Akamaru and which is Naruto...
He can't attack carelessly.
However, it's okay for Naruto-kun
to attack either one!
Oh!
He created a chance opening...
Good work!
I see, so that's your move...
But...
I'll give you a piece of advice!
I was careless before and
a little late to realize it...
But the Transformation Jutsu
isn't effective anymore!
Why, you ask?
Yeah!
I can smell you.
Don't mess with our
sense of smell, Naruto.
By concentrating his Chakra
into his nose,
Kiba's sense of smell is enhanced tens
of thousands of times more than average.
Of course, he can determine
people by their smell too.
Heh, I won!
W-What?!
What's going on?!
Kiba's nose got Naruto and
Akamaru mixed up?
Damn! What in the world is going on...?!
Then you're Naruto!
Messing with me!
What?!
Well, this is coming from
the original prankster, after all...
He's had it!
He did it!
Naruto-kun... Awesome!
Damn it!
So that's it...
Naruto, transformed into Kiba,
was discovered by the real Kiba
with smell and hit...
But Naruto didn't come back
in true Naruto form.
Instead, he transformed into
Akamaru instantly!
In order to make it look as if it
was Akamaru who was hit
and his impersonation
transformation dissolved!
Was Naruto ever that smart...?
You little...!
Think hard about your Jutsu
before you use them!
Because they'll be used
against you, stupid!
He's using my line, word to word...
Arguing with this guy is only
a waste of time!
Don't go at Naruto's pace...
Calm down.
Calm down!
He can't actually keep up with
my movements yet...
I still have the advantage!
Look closely at Naruto's movements
and if there's an opening...
I can surely take him from
behind with the All-Four Jutsu.
Nothing to get flustered about...
If I do this in a level-headed manner,
it's a match I will most certainly win!
Evidently your enemy
has become calm...
Well, what will you do, Naruto...?
So you've finally gotten serious, Kiba?
Well then... I'll end this...
with my new special technique
I've been saving up!
So you've finally gotten serious, Kiba?
Well then... I'll end this...
with my new special technique
I've been saving up!
What?!
New special trick?!
Huh? When did he...?!
Leave it to Naruto-kun to hide
a new technique!
What new special technique!
That's obviously a bluff!
You can test out whether
it's a bluff or not!
This hasn't changed since before...
Don't let his pace get to you.
Calm down!
Let's go!
I don't know what kind of
technique this is but...!
I just won't let you do it!
Now!
Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry...
All-Four Jutsu!
Q-Quick...
Why are you stopping?!
Naruto!
Naruto-kun!
Just as I thought, this is as
far as he will go.
Stand up! Naruto!
D-Damn! I don't even have time
to work up my Chakra!
Hey, hey! What's wrong?!
Naruto!
He's fast!
It's no good.
He doesn't have time to
form hand Signs!
There's too much of a difference
in their strength...
It's impossible for Naruto, after all.
Naruto-kun...
D-Damn!
Take this!
What?!
Take that!
I'm going to be Hokage!
I won't lose here!
Whatever! You can't keep up
with my speed at all!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Naruto!
This is what it's like when
I really let it out.
You understand, don't you?
To me, you're merely...!
I...
Huh?
will absolutely not lose!
That Naruto... He's a fighter.
Yup.
If I were Kiba,
I'd be sick of this already.
It doesn't matter which anymore,
I just wish they'd settle it quickly.
Naruto-kun...
Fight!
Naruto! Use the new technique
or whatever!
Just settle it!
Naruto-kun! Go for it!
I have to find some opening
in that damn Kiba...
You've got absolutely no effect on me!
You've got spirit, I'll give you that!
He's close at his end...
I'll settle it with the next one!
I'll make the new technique
explode no matter what!
I won't let you!
You're slow!
Take this!
Oops!
Fast movements and a keen nose...
The Ninja Art of Beast Mimicry
turned out to be harmful...
Right now Kiba's sense of smell
is tens of thousands times
more powerful than normal...
Well...
That fart was probably
a freak accident, but...
That's what you'd expect from
the number one unpredictable Ninja.
Naruto!
Now's your chance!
Damn!
I was straining too much...
But now's the time to show
my new technique!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Naruto-kun!
Okay! The way you've torn me
apart up until now,
I'll give it back all at once!
D-Damn it!
U-!
Zu-! Ma-! Ki-!
Naruto... Barrage!
A new technique, eh?
Well, he was watching Sasuke's
technique a moment ago...
Lions Barrage!
For the record, the name
is a rip off, too.
The winner is Uzumaki Naruto.
Oh!
Shannaro!
Nice one!
You did it!
That Naruto beat Kiba!
It's a major upset...
Yup!
Yes!
I'm... getting stronger!
That was easy!
W-What to do?
What should I do...?
N-Naruto-kun...
Huh? Hinata?
Did you say something?
Ah, ah, ah...
Umm...
Huh?
Hinata...?
What's this?
It's an ointment.
Why for me?
Take it for her, Naruto.
Hmmm. Okay!
Thank you! You're nice, Hinata!
Kiba, it's nothing to be
embarrassed about ...
This kid was a really
strong opponent.
You are taking this pretty easy,
aren't you, Hinata-sama...?
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
What's with that guy!
Calling people failure and judging them!
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah!
Talking like a wise guy!
I'm in a bad mood!
Hinata, you say something!
Get that guy!
Show that guy that people
can really change!
Next episode:
"Byakugan Unleashed!! The Shy Hinata's daring Determination!"
Go! Fight! Hinata!